# OKIKIOLUWA OLAREWAJU

### **DEVELOPER**



### PROFILE

I'm a research-focused product designer, copy writer and web developer with a great eye for aesthetics and sublime user experience. My expertise lies in user research, quantitative and qualititave analysis, data entry, conceptualizing, designing, and modifying consumer & enterprise products especially web and mobile applications to fit into user expectations and mental models.

## PERSONAL SKILL

- Good Comunication
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Creativity
- Organitation
- Commitment
- Management

#### PERSONAL PROJECT

# 2020 - PRESENT FESAC FOUNDATION

I work as with a non governmental organization to feed educate and save a child. Also design flyer to ensure awareness the my outreach program to eradicate poverty and illiteracy among children

## LANGUAGES

### EDUCATION

2011 - 2017 secondary school certificate

**Faith Academy** 

2017 - 2022 B.sc Mechanical engineering

**Landmark University** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## ► SEPT 2022 - NOV 2022 TESTGORILLA

I worked on building loyalty to ensure long-term client retention by presenting product information, addressing customer issues and helping the sales team with upsells and renewals.

#### ► 2022 - PRESENT FRONTEND DEVELOPER FESAC FOUNDATION

organization to the Globe

Building frontend services and user interfaces to help reach out to sponsors and donors.

Also showcasing mile stones as a non governmental

► 2022 - PRESENT FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER UPWORK & INTERNSHALA

I have worked with frontend technologies/frameworks for years and i build high performant websites that are SEO friendly for clients. I also take into account website load time with image optimisation.

#### **■** EXPERTISE

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Web development, Graphics designer, UI/UX, Software engineer, Transcribing, Copy writing, Customer service, Devops, Data entry and lot more

#### **PREFERED TECHNOLOGIES**

ReactJS , Typescript, Javascript, Tailwind CSS, HTML, Vue js, Figma, Adobe, swift, Xcode, Flutter etc.



